Characters. actions. places. occupations.
and events in this series
are fictional and created
for entertainment purposes only.
They are not intended to urge
or promote any behavior in the series.
Viewer discretion is advised.
Aran. say that again.
You want me to help promote a restaurant?
(The Italian restaurant Mr. Thee gave me.)
You want to go back to work.
don’t you. Lookpeach?
I’ve been thinking about it for a while.
I think it’s time I did something.
Thank you.
You really don’t want to get paid?
It’s fine. Aran.
I haven’t touched a camera in months.
This is good practice for me.
Let me treat you to dinner.
Call it an after-wedding dinner.
The schedule for the grand meeting
has been announced.
What’s going on?
Rome’s going to be ARSENI’s next leader.
taking over from Dad.
SEVEN YEARS AGO
Mr. Krisdanai. you should already
be at the airport by now.
Mr. Kris. I’m not getting in there.
Why not?
I’m working.
Ever since you got transferred here.
do you realize how many times
you’ve said the word ‘work’?
Boss.
I don’t like this version of you. Mok.
Mr. Thee!
Mr. Kris.
Throw him.
-One. Two…
-Don’t!
…three!
Whoo!
You’re going to miss your flight.
Then catch the next one.
He’s already postponed
his flight back to Hong Kong five times.
If he misses this one.
he won’t have enough time
to get ready for school tomorrow.
Then postpone the first day.
We own the school anyway.
Whoo!
Looking for these?
Come and get them.
Rome!
Catch!
Mok. look at me.
I’m way more handsome than you.
“Boss.”
Mr. Thee.
(Kian. can you ask Dad for me?)
(I want to stay here with you and Mok.)
(If that were possible.
I would’ve asked him for myself.)
(Asked him what?)
(Not to leave me here.)
(To let me stay home with you.
Mom. and Dad.)
(Why does ARSENI have to be different?)
(Because it’s ARSENI.)
(That’s why.)
PRESENT DAY
You’ve been in the water for three hours.
Come up already.
Mr. Rome.
Hey!
What the hell are you doing?!
I couldn’t breathe. I could’ve died.
But you didn’t.
Kian. you’re an adult.
Stop acting like a child.
Says the guy who’s running away
from his problems like a child.
Don’t tell people to grow up.
I’m not running away.
I’m just…
Just?
Just what?
I needed some time to think.
And why’d you jump in a suit?
You’re making a mountain
out of a molehill.
You’re jumping at your own shadow.
You’re borrowing trouble.
You’re counting your chickens
before they hatch.
You’re worrying over nothing.
You’re sweating the small stuff—
Hey. hey!
Too much Thai. bro.
I’m not keeping up.
-Kian.
-Rome.
You first.
What the heck?
I’m sorry.
Huh?
For what?
For making everything your burden.
ARSENI.
Dad’s work.
our family business.
Everything.
Take it easy. bro.
If ARSENI needs a leader.
and you don’t want to be one.
then let things unfold
the way they’re meant to.
I already talked to Peach.
Did you stay up all night?
Thinking about Mr. Rome?
What would you say. Lookpeach.
if I were the one who ended up
taking Dad’s place?
I’d just…
keep training in shooting
and martial arts.
And don’t pull your punches—
Even though you could just leave me?
That thought has never crossed my mind.
I’m actually happy
you chose to sacrifice
for your little brother.
Because if I were in your shoes.
I’d do the same.
Usually.
the second heir can
only inherit the leadership if…
the first heir dies
or…
Or what?
Or becomes incapacitated.
and the family agrees he’s unfit to lead.
If Mr. Rome is announced
as the next leader.
people will definitely think less
of Mr. Thee.
That’s the only thing
Mr. Rome is worried about.
So you stormed out of the meeting.
then hid away in the safe house…
all because of this first-heir.
second-heir nonsense?
Mhm.
Your turn.
You apologized and hugged me.
What was that about?
So cringe.
Well…
I was afraid you’d be mad at me
for dumping
all the responsibilities on you
while I lived happily ever after
with Lookpeach here.
Don’t be ridiculous.
If you’re happy. I’m happy.
Right?
I’m your brother.
At least my reason
makes more sense than yours.
You’re worried
people will think badly of me?
Since when have I ever cared
what people think?
So what are you going to do
about the leadership?
Are you going to do what Dad wants?
Let me ask you an honest question. Kian.
You want nothing to do with Dad’s ARSENI
because of Peach. don’t you?
Why would you ask that?
Just answer me.
I just want to spend as much time
with Lookpeach as I can.
What scares me more than my own death
is him dying
because of who we are.
Mm.
I get it.
You know how dangerous Dad’s ARSENI is.
That’s why I want Lookpeach
to stay far away from it.
And he’s not the only one I care about.
I care about you too. Rome.
No worries.
It’s just a slight change of plans.
Instead of being your right-hand man.
I’ll just be the leader.
I get you. though.
Love is just—
You don’t want to drag Mok
into this either. do you?
If staying here is the safer choice.
then I guess I’ll have to give you
your secretary back.
This is the Lee family’s safe house.
We use it to hide from enemies
when danger comes.
Back in the day.
besides being a safe house.
it was a sanctuary for the three of us.
The three of you?
You mean. yourself. Mr. Rome. and Mr. Mok?
Dad brought Mok in to be the wingman
of the next leader.
which was still me back then.
Then he became
the first close friend for both of us.
Mok was taught
to sacrifice his life for us.
So Rome and I made a promise
that we’d protect Mok.
So that no one had to die.
Then. Mok and I were sent to Thailand.
Rome always left Hong Kong
to spend time with us.
When it’s time for him to go back.
we’d hide out here.
Extend our playtime
for two or three hours.
That’s good enough for us.
You were stubborn even as a kid.
Honestly. I was a bit upset
when I learned that Rome thought of Mok
as more than just a friend.
I was afraid I’d be left alone
by the only two friends in my life.
But on second thought.
if it’s the happiness
of the two people I love.
I should be glad.
So that’s the reason.
Because it’s safe here.
you sent Mr. Mok back to your brother
as soon as you could.
I guess so.
(Can)
(you)
(see me?)
(Smile.)
(You’re)
(not)
(alone anymore.)
(I…)
(will walk)
(right beside you.)
This meeting
isn’t about transferring personnel
or expanding our influence
into another continent.
It’s about choosing ARSENI’s next leader
to carry on my work.
You’ve chosen your own path.
I won’t interfere.
This is your territory.
But ARSENI still has to go on.
Krisdanai Rome Lee.
you must prepare yourself
to become ARSENI’s next leader.
Dinner will be ready in ten minutes.
Mr. Thee and Mr. Peach will join you.
Did they say when they’re leaving?
Mr. Thee said
he won’t be staying the night.
Then you should leave with them.
Pardon?
Mr. Rome.
What did you just say?
I never thought
I’d become ARSENI’s leader.
That’s why I fell in love with you.
Mr. Rome…
If I’d known it’d come to this…
I wouldn’t have fallen in love.
Must be nice being an heir
to the Lee family.
Whether to love or not…
you get to decide for yourself.
Fine.
If that’s the Boss’s order.
I’ll obey.
I have no right to question it.
So this is why ARSENI’s bodyguards
have to stay away from love.
What do you know?
I may not know all the details.
but everyone in ARSENI knows about…
the relationship
between you and Mr. Krisdanai.
ARSENI bodyguards
are trained to expect death.
and they’re not allowed to fall in love.
If you want to stay here.
you’d better remember that.
You made that last part up yourself.
Mr. Mok.
Ms. Mira. don’t listen to him.
ARSENI isn’t that heartless.
Being a bodyguard is just a job.
You don’t have to cut your heart out
before you come to work.
Besides. you couldn’t do that yourself.
Mr. Mok.
So don’t expect Ms. Mira to.
Mr. Peach.
You were taught to shoot
with your right hand.
just like P’Kian.
But now you shoot with your left.
just like Mr. Rome.
I call that love.
What do you think. Mr. Mok?
I don’t know. sir.
Right now. I don’t know anything.
I think…
you should give Mr. Rome some time.
I’m sure he has his reasons.
And not loving you isn’t one of them.
As for you. Ms. Mira.
you’re allowed to love here.
You should’ve dropped me off
at work first.
Now Mr. Mok has to drive me back
to the studio.
We’ve got two hours
before you have to be there.
There’s no way I’m wasting that.
Peach.
Hey.
I missed you.
Ew.
You didn’t wash your hair again. did you?
Come on. Peach.
I washed it this morning.
I’m just teasing.
Just in case I was right.
You said you missed me. huh?
You haven’t come home in days.
You sure you missed me?
Thee’s house is pretty far.
My condo is way closer.
Next time. we can come to work together.
If you’re worried about losing sleep.
how about we buy an RV?
That way you can get a little more rest.
You can even shower here.
That’s true.
I’d never be late to clock in
if I came with you.
Oh.
Clock in…
What is it?
I was in such a rush to see you.
I forgot to clock in.
I’m late.
What?
Let’s do this.
I’ll go left. and you go right.
Okay?
Yes. ma’am.
Is it almost time for work?
Yes.
Then let me drive you to work.
No.
Why not?
Because we’ve been back and forth between
ARSENI and the studio enough times.
See you.
We’ve still got time.
Let’s hang out at ARSENI for a bit first.
Huh?
We’ve still got time.
Let me drive you to work.
Huh?
What should I do now?
I’m all out of excuses.
You should let me go to work.
I’ll see you in the evening.
I need one last refill.
Refill?
A refill of you…
to hold me over until I see you again.
That’s enough.
Let me go to work.
I’ll see you tonight.
We can’t keep doing this every day.
How about this?
I’ll go drink coffee at ARSENI.
Then we can part ways there.
Deal?
You act so nonchalant.
but you don’t want to be apart
from me either.
I’ll have my buddy Mok
prepare you a coffee.
I already have one.
Oh?
Well…
Then I’ll find you a nice. cozy spot
where you can sip it nice and slow.
It’s time.
Playtime’s over.
I really have to go now.
After everything I did
to make you all mine.
you still went and got yourself a job
at another company.
What more do I have to do?
Give me the car keys.
I’ll pick you up this evening.
Have Mok drive you.
That way. I’ll know you’re safe.
Wait here.
As soon as the car’s ready.
I’ll have someone come get you.
You miss him. don’t you?
Oops!
Quit fooling around.
You really think glasses and an earpiece
are enough to fool me?
But in that drama. the heroine only
puts on a fake mustache.
and the male lead can’t recognize her.
That’s a drama.
10 MINUTES EARLIER
Mr. Thee.
My buddy Thee.
What is it. sir?
Take your clothes off.
What?
Call Peach the way you always do.
“Mr. Peach.”
Mr. Peach.
No. do it again.
Peach. Peach.
Mr. Peach.
Mr. Peach. Mr. Peach.
Give me those too.
For the perfect disguise.
Mr. Peach. Mr. Peach.
Peach. Peach.
Peach.
That’s perfect?
How do I look?
Do I look cool?
Hello.
Hi.
I’m returning the camera.
You can borrow mine.
If we run into each other
at a studio someday.
just give it back then.
I’m a first-year photography student.
Wait.
First-year?
How did you end up working here?
Oh!
I’m on a scholarship.
so I help out at the university.
I got to know a lot of professors.
so I asked if I could intern
at a production studio.
I do a little bit of everything.
Help out on set and carry equipment.
And…
I wanted to see you.
just like we promised.
I’m really glad we finally met.
And I’m happy
to see you chasing your dream.
It might be a small first step.
but you’ve already taken it.
Thank you.
Hey. how about this?
Since we finally met.
would you like to be my assistant?
I’ll talk to the producer for you.
I’d love to.
Drive faster. M2.
Peach is about to get off work. right. M1?
M? What’s that. sir?
Mok and Mira.
Ah.
According to the breakdown
Mr. Peach sent us.
they haven’t even shot the last setup yet.
I miss him like crazy.
If you miss him.
why not send him a text?
Absolutely not.
I don’t want to interrupt him
while he’s working.
Peach needs to stay focused.
Yes. sir.
SOMETHING AMAZING HAPPENED.
I’LL TELL YOU WHEN I GET HOME.
Amazing?
How did Peach call this ‘amazing’?
The company that hired Peach today.
buy it!
You just said you didn’t want to
interrupt him at work.
Are they hugging?
It’s fine.
At least they’re keeping a safe distance.
And what’s with that stupid mini heart?
Damn it!
About buying that company.
should we treat that as an actual order?
You did a great job today.
See you at the next shoot.
Thank you. Peach.
I’m really glad we met.
See you.
Sure. See you.
The day after tomorrow?
Let me check Mr. Thee’s schedule first.
I think we can make it.
(Okay.)
(I’ve come up with
a bunch of new dishes with the chef.)
(and you and Mr. Thee
get to try them first.)
Wow. Aran.
That’s very scary.
Are you sure they’re edible?
(Come on. Peach.)
I’m kidding.
(Um…)
(What color should the theme be?)
What? Do we really need one?
(Of course.)
(It’s your post-wedding dinner.
after all.)
(Let’s go with a peach theme.)
(Is there anything special you’d like?)
(Just let me know.)
(I’ll make it happen.)
Actually…
There is one little thing I’d like to ask.
I got home too late to tuck them in.
It’s one of the reasons
I don’t want to go back to work.
I’m afraid I won’t be able to fulfill
my duties as a father.
But I know you can handle it all
at the same time. P’Kian.
Even so…
I still can’t help worrying.
Back at Baan Klamai.
Mother kept a little doll
for each of us to represent her.
since she couldn’t tuck everyone
in every night.
A doll?
Yeah.
Poor you.
You were raised just like Punch-kun.
Should we get them
a little doll to represent us
on the nights we have to come home late?
We should. Peach-kun.
Are you working?
Are you free the day after tomorrow?
Aran invited us to his restaurant.
He’s treating us to a post-wedding dinner
because he couldn’t make it
to our wedding.
Every second of my time belongs to you.
So…
feel free to schedule it however you want.
This is unacceptable!
What is?
The cast that Director Nuttapong
chose to star in Me and Thee.
One look. and I can already tell
there’s no way this guy can play me.
Na-ra-vit?
For a boy band member.
he’s not even as fit as I am.
And look at that innocent face.
Who’s going to believe
he has a wolf tattoo across his chest?
Forget holding a gun.
I couldn’t have been any cooler that day.
This dude’s going to ruin my heroic moment
when I saved you from Wiwid.
Phuwin.
That’s a cool name.
Not as cool as Peachayarat.
But he looks…
adorable.
Adorable?
Uh-huh.
Looks like Mr. Phuwin here
is about to become your new lemur.
No.
He’s not.
Is something wrong?
I just don’t like hearing you
talk about other people like that.
On the honor of the Lee family.
I swear I’ll never call anyone else
“adorable.”
That word belongs to my life partner alone.
Okay.
That goes for “so cute.”
“good-looking.”
“gorgeous.”
“pretty.”
and every other word
that could give people the wrong idea.
Those words are reserved
for you and you alone. Lookpeach.
I like it.
Like what?
I like it when you’re jealous.
I’m not the jealous one.
That’s you. P’Kian.
Mr. Mok told me—
You got the wrong end of the slick.
‘Stick.’
If I were jealous.
that would mean I don’t trust you.
That day will never come.
I know that even if the sky fell
and the earth crumbled.
you’d still love only me.
Did you really think
that ridiculous photo
you sent would make me cry?
I’m not the old Theerakit anymore.
This Theerakit finally got a grip…
and also got lots of money.
So.
live the life you want.
Don’t worry about a thing.
I just didn’t like that kid
making a mini heart
and putting his arm around your shoulder.
Lucky for him. I wasn’t there.
Otherwise. I’d…
Well…
Your smile belongs to me.
I can’t help it.
Theerakit Kian Lee is possessive.
That’s why he has a wolf
biting a peach tattooed right here.
Or maybe I should engrave my name on you.
so no one else thinks about
laying a finger on you.
You broadcast your proposal
to the whole country.
That’s even bigger than
engraving your name on me.
All of me is already yours.
Your name’s been engraved in here…
for a long time.
What a ridiculous thing to say.
I had no idea
you were this whipped. Lookpeach.
You stole my line.
What are you doing. P’Kian?
Is it a surprise?
I’m so excited.
Ready?
I’m going to uncover your eyes.
Ta-da!
-Whoa!
What is this?
A small doll to tuck our kids
in whenever we can’t.
Thank you. Dad.
This is cute.
No problem.
It’s literally our size.
I haven’t seen Lookplub in ages.
Back when we were working
on the ARSENI project together.
we saw each other all the time.
I kind of miss those days.
Hey. just a heads-up.
Lookplub’s even feistier than Peach.
So be on your best behavior
when you meet her.
Tawan.
You okay?
Aran.
Don’t you ever miss working in showbiz?
Why do you ask?
Whenever you talk about it.
you seem so happy.
Your eyes light up. You know?
So…
Do I look unhappy when I’m with you?
That’s not what I meant.
You stop taking on projects
because of me. don’t you?
I don’t want to upset you again.
And things are finally going so well.
I’m scared that
one wrong move
will bring us right back to where we were.
Listen to me.
Things aren’t the way they used to be.
I’ll never
throw away the last chance you gave me.
Please trust me. Aran.
Thank you
for changing for me.
I should thank you…
for taking in a lost puppy like me.
A lost puppy?
That’s too cute for you.
You’re not even cute.
And yet you still can’t stop liking me.
Hm?
I never said I liked you. roommate.
Fine. You don’t like me.
But I’ll make you fall
head over heels for me.
Now go.
Check on the food in the kitchen.
Peach will be here soon.
Go on.
Why are you smiling?
I’m not.
This literally is a chef’s table.
Wow. Aran.
You didn’t have to do this much.
If I’m going to do it.
I might as well do it right.
Have a seat.
Looking good.
I…
I did something for Mr. Thee.
I finished it a while ago.
but I don’t know how to give it to him.
What is it?
Excuse me. I need to use the ladies’ room.
Oh. hi.
Why are you standing out here
feeding the mosquitoes?
Aren’t you gonna eat?
It’s okay.
Would you like to come in with me?
It’s okay. ma’am.
It’s going to be a performance.
I’m—
I’m going to sing and play the guitar.
Come on.
They’re not going to yell at you.
Uh…
Please?
Come on.
I’m nervous.
I need someone to cheer me on. Yeah?
I think I’d rather stay out here.
All right. then.
Ms. Panachakorn.
Break a leg.
Thank you.
Ahem.
Good evening.
Whoo!
The song I’m about to sing
was written straight from the heart
of Mr. Peachayarat Jane-kit…
Oops.
I mean. Lee.
It’s how he feels about his life partner.
Aww!
Enough talking.
Just sing already.
You wrote a song. Peach?
There’s just one problem.
What is it?
I did try…
but I really can’t sing.
What’s going on here?
♪ Since the day
I finally found the answer ♪
♪ It’s you who’s worth
more than any treasure ♪
♪ I need nothing more
just you here with me ♪
♪ And you’ll always be
the only one my eyes will see ♪
♪ No matter what we face
no matter how much time goes by ♪
♪ You’re still the only one
who owns this heart of mine ♪
♪ I’ll rest at this place.
right here with you ♪
♪ I fall in love with you ♪
♪ You’re my only focus ♪
♪ You’re the only one I’m searching for ♪
♪ No matter how the world keeps turning ♪
♪ You’re the one I adore ♪
♪ Every second belongs to you ♪
♪ You’re my only focus ♪
May I have this dance. Mr. Theerakit?
♪ Though the days pass by.
you’re all I see ♪
♪ I’ll love. love only you ♪
♪ Forever only choosing you still ♪
♪ No matter what we face
no matter how much time goes by ♪
♪ You’re still the only one
who owns this heart of mine ♪
A surprise for me. baby?
I…
I wrote this song a long time ago.
After you proposed to me.
I wanted to give something back
for all the love you’ve given me.
But what else could I do?
I can’t sing.
Even if you just read the lyrics.
they’ll still sound like music to my ears.
♪ You’re the only one I’m searching for ♪
♪ Though the days pass by.
you’re all I see ♪
♪ I’ll love. love only you ♪
♪ Forever only choosing you still ♪
Mr. Mok.
You couldn’t even pass the first test.
How am I supposed to trust you
with Mr. Theerakit?
I’m sorry.
(There are some moments of yours
that you never get to see.)
(But I do.)
What is this?
It’s our post-wedding dinner.
Of course it can’t be ordinary.
(This is when you’re asleep.)
(You probably don’t know
that you look so cute when you sleep.)
(That’s why I love watching you.)
(Back then. I could only steal glances.)
(Now I’ve been watching you sleep
for over three months. )
(As long as there’s another morning.)
(let me wake up beside you
and watch you sleep. stubborn one.)
I loved you so much before.
but today.
I love you a thousand times more.
and I’ll never stop loving you.
Be my dance partner
for the rest of our lives.
Until my very last breath.
I told you before that
I couldn’t get more tattoos
because it hurt.
So instead. I wrote it down.
Forever Only Choosing You Still.
Let’s go. Mr. Thee.
Whoo!
Over here.
Throw it this way. Peach!
Give me that.
Right here!
One. two. three!
Aran. did you know
the person who catches the flowers
is supposed to get married next?
And this is the part
where they kiss. right?
Kiss!
I know you’re shy.
So. don’t worry.
No one’s going to see you.
Oh. come on.
Don’t block the view.
-They won’t let us see.
-Exactly.
Come on. show us!
Remove your jacket.
Yeah. don’t cover up.
What?
Aw. come on!
We can’t see.
Oh. come on.
Don’t block the view.
They won’t let us see.
I know you’re shy.
No one’s going to see you.
♪ You’re my only focus ♪
♪ I only need you. nothing more ♪
♪ Though the days pass by.
you’re all I see ♪
♪ I’ll love. love only you ♪
♪ Forever only choosing you still ♪
I planned to surprise you.
but ended up being the one surprised.
Keeping the distance
to find out how you really feel.
Keep playing hard to get.
and you’ll be left on the shelf forever.
Like you’re some kind of love expert.
At least I have a marriage certificate.
Don’t ever do this in my territory again.
I can’t bear to see Mok hurt anymore.
What do you want from us?
You feel guilty
for putting everyone at risk.
How could this possibly
be your fault. P’Kian?
Thank you for being strong
on the day I wasn’t.
Because we’re partners for life.